Hello.
Welcome back.
In this lesson, we are going to see how to download Cube M X five and the new cube IDC released by
S-T Micro-electronics.
So I'm a Google over here.
I'm simply going to search download SDM 32 Cube remix.
Okay, let's see so we can come to the S-T dot com.
That's the official Web site of STK Micro-electronics.
Click over here, open in a tab over here.
And here it is.
As crude own.
And I'll click get software.
The latest version is five point five, as we can see over here, over here.
If you want to select a previous version, you can select that as well.
I'll just click get software over here.
And it gives this license agreement.
I've read this before, so I'll simply go ahead and accept.
Once that is done, you've got to input your e-mail address and your name over here.
And once I looked in, I'm brought back here.
Click, download.
So the first time I said get software, you can either click, download or wait for the download to
begin automatically as it has begun over here.
So it is downloading it now.
Right.
The download is complete.
I'm going to download the SDM 30 to Cube.
This a new IDC released by S.T. Microelectronics say SDM 32 or SDM Cube?
IDC said it's called.
Put load here.
And then, all right, click over here.
So this idea is free of charge.
And there are no, quote, limits, unlike Karl, your vision, where the trial version gives you 32
kilobytes of code limit.
This one here, you can have however large your code is and it's all for free.
So I'm brought over here.
I can download the version that corresponds to my operating system.
I'm currently running Windows.
As you can see.
So I'm going to click this over here for the Windows install.
I get software
and this license and agreement is brought up again.
I'm going to accept.
And we brought here again.
I'll log in.
And it's going to start automatically.
My computer's a bit slow today, okay?
It started downloading, let's call it both.
Six hundred and sixty five megabyte.
So this would take a while.
So in the next lesson, we shall see how to install both the SDM 32 Cuba mix and the SDM 32 cube IDC.
I'll see you in the next lesson.